Guide to the Teamsters Local 294 Records, 1906-1983 IBT.0083
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Teamsters Local 294 Records
1906-1983
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT.0083
2 Cubic feet 1 record center carton, 1 oversize flat gray
good
This collection contains materials from Teamsters local 294. Box 1 contains dues cards, photographs, minute books, and bylaws. Box 2 contains copies of The Upstate New Yorker newspaper.
Content Description
This collection contains labor newspapers, dues cards, by-laws and minute books from Teamsters Local 294.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical / Historical
Teamsters Local 294, based in Albany, New York, is among the oldest Teamster local unions. IBT Local 182 and Brewery Workers Union Local 1015 later merged into Local 294.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred from IBT, 2017 017.
General
- Dues Cards Local 294, 1906-1921 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Scanned Agreements, 1917-1918 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Local Elections Materials, 1983-1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Local 182 Bylaws, ND (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Photographs, ND (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Iron Molders Union No. 8 Badge, ND (Box 1, Folder 6)
- AFL News Reporter Newspaper, 1953-1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Upstate New Yorker Newspapers, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Upstate New Yorker Newspapers, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Upstate New Yorker Newspapers, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Upstate New Yorker Newspapers, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Upstate New Yorker Newspapers, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Upstate New Yorker Newspapers, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Upstate New Yorker Newspapers, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Upstate New Yorker Newspapers, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Upstate New Yorker Newspapers, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Upstate New Yorker Newspaper Book, 1951-1957 (Box 2, Item 1)
- Upstate New Yorker Newspaper Book, 1960 (Box 2, Item 2)
- Upstate New Yorker Newspaper Book, 1961 (Box 2, Item 3)
- Upstate New Yorker Newspaper Book, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Item 4)
- Local 294 Minute Book, 1938-1940 (Box 1, Item 1)
- Local 294 Minute Book, 1940 (Box 1, Item 2)
- Local 294 Minute Book, 1940-1944 (Box 1, Item 3)
- Local 294 Minute Book, 1949 (Box 1, Item 4)
- Local 294 Minute Book, 1953-1955 (Box 1, Item 5)
- Local 294 Minute Book, 1956-1958 (Box 1, Item 6)
- Local 294 Minute Book, 1959-1964 (Box 1, Item 7)
- Copies of Town's Agreements to PERB, 1978-1994 (Box 1, Item 8)
- Local 1015 Brewery Workers Union Minute Book, 1976-1980 (Box 1, Item 9)